esta noche doctor applicable Metro will
be inducted by Richard foam core he's
the managing partner of ma I Capital
Management LLC as a full-service wealth
man who are dedicated to creating a
culture that promotes collaboration
innovation areas will change but he is a
better person than he has pulmonologist
is the most caring loving person that
I've ever met in my life is quite
extremist hearing audience tonight is
the beautiful daughter the son and why
the son and his son's future to wake and
work with me it's little grand when a
coke that was here to comment but this
man is truly when you look at the
dictionary Haddock Webster's dictionary
I've heard the doctor and his pictures
because he is everything that doctor is
supposed to be not just from the medical
point of view but from the personal
point of view and when I wanted you to
share our story and tell me how close
we've become because of it he is a truly
a brother to me obviously everyone here
is been inducted by someone of their own
culture we are brothers so it's our
culture on the county he's Indian but I
feel closer to him than I do almost
anything else in the world so four years
ago my wife was dying many years ago
diagnosed with interstitial lung disease
which is an autoimmune problem that
eventually deteriorate sure Lana's a new
introduced dr. Mehta and asked him to
take care of her and the first thing he
said was that is one of the greatest
honors of my life that you asked me to
take care of your weapon how many
doctors say that to you surely have to
be mended and you would think me that's
a line right it's when he really
believes it's true we didn't went
through the process of getting
transplant test under his great guidance
and leadership we then cut a team on the
list we had two calls where they call
you up and say come to the hospital
prepare us and that's what they say
sorry the lung stay at work this is
where this man jumps right into the
spray it says you know what it wasn't
meant to be there a better one who see
you coming he knows what to say he knows
how to prepare you do you know how to
take care of you just not from the
medical but from the heart and there's
nobody better in the world I've ever
seen in this man you doing so long story
short we finally get our lungs December
17th we get the call he calls us and
says report to the hospital at 10
o'clock at night we get there to where
he's prepped 1:30 in the morning they
say it's a go she gets rolled into
Beemer operating at 3 o'clock in the
morning that my son showed up to be with
me because it's a long way that's a long
operation she probably can I knew we
were waiting the whole time so then
about 8 o'clock we come straight to a
benefit and you walked right up to my
son and he says your son which is
exactly what needed to be said at that
point in time because of all the
pressure all the anguish that you're
feeling and he did that throughout the
whole thing and he's been there are
guardian angel this whole time so when I
say you you know everyone up here is so
deserving that this man saves lives he
saves families he kept me in the love of
my life
we were blessed and thankful every day
we have and so I can't tell you how much
I love him and care for him but he is so
deserving of this report and so well
represented here tonight by his
communion representatives and friends
but this trend will be his brother
forever so with great pleasure and honor
I want to welcome dr. Atul Medical
[Applause]